[{"answer": "Piers, I'm sensational.", "docId": "140131pmt", "aSentId": 22, "question": "Joe, how are you?", "qSentId": 21}, {"answer": "This whole issue that's been going on for the last couple of years, you know ...", "docId": "140131pmt", "aSentId": 33, "question": "What was going on that made you think, \"Some thing's not right here\"?", "qSentId": 32}, {"answer": "Not that I might know it.", "docId": "140131pmt", "aSentId": 47, "question": "You were disconcerted after all that hitting?", "qSentId": 46}, {"answer": "I wouldn't say killed off because through the process that I've experienced, they regenerate it.", "docId": "140131pmt", "aSentId": 50, "question": "So when they discovered that you had gotten these brain cells which slowed down or being killed off, how would you describe that?", "qSentId": 49}, {"answer": "You know, I was feeling pretty good ahead of time before ...", "docId": "140131pmt", "aSentId": 52, "question": "And do you personally feel better for this treatment?", "qSentId": 51}, {"answer": "Oh dear, it's even worse than I thought.", "docId": "140131pmt", "aSentId": 63, "question": "What game?", "qSentId": 62}, {"answer": "I wish I knew.", "docId": "140131pmt", "aSentId": 65, "question": "Who's going to win?", "qSentId": 64}, {"answer": "Maybe not the temperature when you a little bit cold.", "docId": "140131pmt", "aSentId": 74, "question": "Should it make any difference to a great player whether it's a little bit cold or warm?", "qSentId": 73}, {"answer": "My gut reaction is, \"Oh man, you know, that's not cool.\"", "docId": "140131pmt", "aSentId": 91, "question": "What's your gut reaction to that?", "qSentId": 90}, {"answer": "We were 17 and 19 point underdog ...", "docId": "140131pmt", "aSentId": 110, "question": "But you weren't even favorites, right?", "qSentId": 109}, {"answer": "My money's going to be in my pocket to use at the grocery store, man.", "docId": "140131pmt", "aSentId": 124, "question": "What do you think?", "qSentId": 123}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "140131pmt", "aSentId": 135, "question": "Do you resent the fact you had to pay for a drink and a meal in the city?", "qSentId": 134}, {"answer": "I think I can say that with some qualification, it will not be snowing.", "docId": "140131pmt", "aSentId": 167, "question": "Are you sure?", "qSentId": 166}, {"answer": "PRESIDENT & CEO, NY/NJ SUPER BOWL HOST COMMITTEE: Well, exactly how much of that really is myth versus reality.", "docId": "140131pmt", "aSentId": 191, "question": "How do you deal with issues like that on the peripheral (ph) of the actual game?", "qSentId": 190}, {"answer": "Yeah, I mean I think that there has to be a code of conduct.", "docId": "140131pmt", "aSentId": 212, "question": "But does that carry with it a responsibility to always conduct themselves to the best possible level?", "qSentId": 211}, {"answer": "But this is the media fanning an issue because it sells newspapers and it gets people to watch TV.", "docId": "140131pmt", "aSentId": 222, "question": "Jon?", "qSentId": 221}, {"answer": "No, not you personally, no.", "docId": "140131pmt", "aSentId": 224, "question": "Are you blaming me jobless?", "qSentId": 223}, {"answer": "Yeah, I like to see just, just speaking for me, I think everybody has got their point of view.", "docId": "140131pmt", "aSentId": 233, "question": "What is that thing you really want to talk?", "qSentId": 232}, {"answer": "The team with the most points.", "docId": "140131pmt", "aSentId": 238, "question": "Finally, just very quickly, one word answer or two word answers, who is going to win?", "qSentId": 237}, {"answer": "Right.", "docId": "140131pmt", "aSentId": 246, "question": "Woody?", "qSentId": 245}, {"answer": "Well, it's hard to get a bet against Peyton.", "docId": "140131pmt", "aSentId": 252, "question": "Where's your money at?", "qSentId": 251}, {"answer": "Of course the Seahawks just because he wants to (inaudible).", "docId": "140131pmt", "aSentId": 264, "question": "Who are you rooting for?", "qSentId": 263}, {"answer": "Hi Piers.", "docId": "140131pmt", "aSentId": 281, "question": "Dan, how are you?", "qSentId": 280}, {"answer": "Well, you know, I think it's going to be a close game because these two teams -- and the match up I look at is Peyton Manning having the great year's offense -- number one offense in league, number one defense in Seattle.", "docId": "140131pmt", "aSentId": 290, "question": "And let's talk about the game on Sunday, who's going to win?", "qSentId": 289}, {"answer": "Right.", "docId": "140131pmt", "aSentId": 301, "question": "However, I do know this, I know this Peyton Manning is massive like you and Russell Wilson, his quarterback opponent, is a tiny guy by comparison, right, by the look?", "qSentId": 300}, {"answer": "Well, I think first all is the experience.", "docId": "140131pmt", "aSentId": 303, "question": "How much does that come into play in a Super Bowl if it's all (ph)?", "qSentId": 302}, {"answer": "You know, I think he's going to continue to play either way.", "docId": "140131pmt", "aSentId": 318, "question": "You know, this could be the great swan song or it could be a bit of a dance group for him, couldn't it?", "qSentId": 317}, {"answer": "Yes, in London, yes.", "docId": "140131pmt", "aSentId": 326, "question": "You did?", "qSentId": 325}, {"answer": "You know what...", "docId": "140131pmt", "aSentId": 331, "question": "But, how do you feel about never having won a Super Bowl?", "qSentId": 330}, {"answer": "I'll tell you what it does affect me though, is when I watch the Super Bowl, you know, I feel -- I looked at it and after the game is over and someone's holding up the trophies and I say, you know, I never had that feeling.", "docId": "140131pmt", "aSentId": 334, "question": "You sit in your cabin -- low cabin at night and go what the hell happened?", "qSentId": 333}, {"answer": "That's what the players called.", "docId": "140131pmt", "aSentId": 349, "question": "Do you actually start saying Hail Mary?", "qSentId": 348}, {"answer": "It was really, really important, you know, but that's what the play -- the play was called.", "docId": "140131pmt", "aSentId": 358, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 357}, {"answer": "I'm not going to answer that.", "docId": "140131pmt", "aSentId": 386, "question": "Is he being a bit of a wusser (ph)?", "qSentId": 385}, {"answer": "I wasn't...", "docId": "140131pmt", "aSentId": 423, "question": "Could you (inaudible) a lot of that?", "qSentId": 422}, {"answer": "Good to see you.", "docId": "140131pmt", "aSentId": 443, "question": "Curt, how are you?", "qSentId": 442}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "140131pmt", "aSentId": 453, "question": "Do you agree with it?", "qSentId": 452}, {"answer": "I think Bruno Mars -- and I'm not joking about this, will be brilliant.", "docId": "140131pmt", "aSentId": 508, "question": "More importantly where is Bruno Mars going to rank in the pantheon of great half time acts (ph)?", "qSentId": 507}, {"answer": "I've been to the opera.", "docId": "140131pmt", "aSentId": 533, "question": "Are you (inaudible) to your opera, Curt?", "qSentId": 532}, {"answer": "Because as much as you can seat up close...", "docId": "140131pmt", "aSentId": 538, "question": "You do?", "qSentId": 537}, {"answer": "No, men too.", "docId": "140131pmt", "aSentId": 544, "question": "You face the (inaudible) and look at women's legs, huh?", "qSentId": 543}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "140131pmt", "aSentId": 546, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 545}, {"answer": "I'm good.", "docId": "140131pmt", "aSentId": 592, "question": "How are you?", "qSentId": 591}, {"answer": "I didn't know.", "docId": "140131pmt", "aSentId": 595, "question": "You have grossed -- do you know of this, in 10 movies, you have grossed worldwide box office takings of $1.5 billion?", "qSentId": 594}, {"answer": "You know, I love -- I love the president and I think he's doing good.", "docId": "140131pmt", "aSentId": 605, "question": "How do you think he's doing since we last met?", "qSentId": 604}, {"answer": "And, you know, I like football.", "docId": "140131pmt", "aSentId": 610, "question": "Are you a football man?", "qSentId": 609}, {"answer": "You know what, I don't have a team, team but I like individual the players.", "docId": "140131pmt", "aSentId": 615, "question": "Who's your team?", "qSentId": 614}, {"answer": "I played but I broke both of my wrists in practice.", "docId": "140131pmt", "aSentId": 633, "question": "Did you ever play?", "qSentId": 632}, {"answer": "Yeah, man.", "docId": "140131pmt", "aSentId": 636, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 635}, {"answer": "Mr. Crabtree.", "docId": "140131pmt", "aSentId": 648, "question": "Who was talking about you?", "qSentId": 647}, {"answer": "Yeah, you know, I guess he was in a moment because I think he's a great guy but that's a -- I think he -- he apologized and went there -- he probably went home and saw that and like \"Oh, that was too much.\"", "docId": "140131pmt", "aSentId": 655, "question": "Isn't that why we watch football for characters to show passion?", "qSentId": 654}, {"answer": "Well, you know, I met Justin a few times and he's a great kid.", "docId": "140131pmt", "aSentId": 674, "question": "And what do you think of Justin Bieber's problems alone?", "qSentId": 673}, {"answer": "Well, you know, I'll tell him, you know, I try to tell him that he could tell me anything and we could talk about anything because I know he's going to go through, you know, all the stuff that I've been through but I want him to handle it well, you know.", "docId": "140131pmt", "aSentId": 683, "question": "What advice do you give him about the real world of pitfalls certainly given the famous dad and so on?", "qSentId": 682}, {"answer": "It's different.", "docId": "140131pmt", "aSentId": 690, "question": "Is fame cloud a corrosive drug in your experience?", "qSentId": 689}, {"answer": "OK.", "docId": "140131pmt", "aSentId": 709, "question": "I'll tell you a speech on the State of the Union and how it applies to you personally, Chris Tucker?", "qSentId": 708}, {"answer": "You know what, I don't know, I don't know but I know he's such - he's doing such a good job to me because I think he's - because he does more - he does what he could do as president but now, he just have some morals in some certain things he stand for.", "docId": "140131pmt", "aSentId": 722, "question": "Do you think Barack Obama, being president, for five odd years now, did he made America more or less racist having its first black president?", "qSentId": 721}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "140131pmt", "aSentId": 726, "question": "Do you think he's found that the problem of being president is it's very hard to get the stuff you really want done done?", "qSentId": 725}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "140131pmt", "aSentId": 728, "question": "And you're in a war zone everyday?", "qSentId": 727}, {"answer": "I remember doing -- yeah, cleaning at night.", "docId": "140131pmt", "aSentId": 769, "question": "Do you remember working at Burger King?", "qSentId": 768}, {"answer": "Funniest person I ever seen was -- you know, my family is funny but with far as entertainment, you know, Richard Pryor, Eddie Murphy.", "docId": "140131pmt", "aSentId": 780, "question": "Who is the funniest person you've ever seen?", "qSentId": 779}, {"answer": "It might be true, you know.", "docId": "140131pmt", "aSentId": 791, "question": "Do you agree with that prediction?", "qSentId": 790}]